<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CSU R Users Group website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CSU R Users Group website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Location</title>
      <link>/2019/05/28/new-location/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/28/new-location/</guid>
      <description>Hello all,
Just a reminder that we have a new location for the summer. We will be meeting at the Treehouse Conference Room, NR 360 for the remainder of the summer.
This coming Wed will be a working meeting, so bring your R questions!
See you tomorrow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer meeting times</title>
      <link>/2019/05/20/summer-meeting-times/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/20/summer-meeting-times/</guid>
      <description>Hello all!
Hopefully everyone survived the semester in one piece.
We are going to continue to meet over the summer, but are changing the meeting day to Wednesdays from 3-5. Our first meeting of the summer will be this coming Wed, May 22. We will be meeting in our usual location (Plant Sciences E005).
Next week we will be moving to Natural Resources 360 (The Treehouse Conference Room). Fancy!
Hope to see you this Wed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R Fundamentals</title>
      <link>/2019/05/13/r_fundamentals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/13/r_fundamentals/</guid>
      <description>Hello R-users,
This week, Matt will talk about how R works at a base level, including the Read Eval Print Loop, parsing of R code, scoping rules and how R finds variables and functions, and R&amp;rsquo;s data types.
We will also chat about a plan for the summer. If you&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to participate in R-group this spring but we&amp;rsquo;re able to because of scheduling now is the time to speak up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed models using lme4 and nlme</title>
      <link>/2019/04/29/mixed_models/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/29/mixed_models/</guid>
      <description>Hello R-users,
On Monday, April 29, Scott Haley will walk us through the basics of implementing mixed effects models in R. We&amp;rsquo;ll walk through differences between two packages commonly used for these models: nlme and lme4. Feel free to bring your own data to work with or just follow along with the group.
Hope to see you there! Plant Sciences C005 3pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning and plotting date/time data in R</title>
      <link>/2019/04/15/datetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/15/datetime/</guid>
      <description>Hi all! Today Magda Garbowski will be giving a short talk on cleaning and plotting date/time data in R. Materials for this talk can be found here.
The talk will last approximately 30 minutes, followed by an open work session. Please feel free to come by for the talk, the work session, or both!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Work Day</title>
      <link>/2019/04/01/work-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/01/work-day/</guid>
      <description>Hello all! We will be having an open work day today.
Please feel free to drop in any time between 3-5 with your R questions, or just hang out with some like-minded R users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our new site!</title>
      <link>/2019/03/08/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/03/08/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the new website for the CSU R Users Group.
Here, you will find the latest announcements from our mailing list about upcoming events, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a group of R users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>13 May 2019: R Fundamentals  Matt Espe will talk about how R works at a base level, including the Read Eval Print Loop, parsing of R code, scoping rules and how R finds variables and functions, and R&amp;rsquo;s data types.
Past Talks  29 April 2019: Mixed models using lme4 and nlme  Scott Haley will walk us through the basics of implementing mixed effects models in R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>